export const AnimalQuestions = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Which of the following animals is highly intelligent and very playful?",
      choices: ["Penguin", "Dolphin", "Elephant", "Crocodile"],
      correctAnswer: "Dolphin",
      fact: "Dolphins have been observed using tools, such as using sponges to protect their snouts while foraging for food on the ocean floor.",
      id: "c7c14b91-c362-4c28-b70b-2f800156c1eb"
    },
    {
      question: "Which large land animal is known for its long trunk, big ears, and tusks?",
      choices: ["Elephant", "Lion", "Pig", "Zebra"],
      correctAnswer: "Elephant",
      fact: "The African elephant, known for its long trunk, big ears, and tusks, is the largest land animal on Earth.",
      id: "974e6daa-035e-4b94-a974-8037b0ad41d8"
    },
    {
      question: "Which wild animal is often referred to as the \"king of the jungle\"?",
      choices: ["Lion", "Giraffe", "Elephant", "Wolf"],
      correctAnswer: "Lion",
      fact: "The lion, often referred to as the \"king of the jungle,\" is known for its majestic appearance and powerful roar.",
      id: "3a3b8335-af13-4760-93ed-0d1009009c1a"
    },
    {
      question: "Which domesticated animal is commonly kept for its milk and meat?",
      choices: ["Sheep", "Pig", "Cow", "Horse"],
      correctAnswer: "Cow",
      fact: "Cows are one of the primary sources of dairy products worldwide, providing milk for drinking, cheese, butter, and other dairy products.",
      id: "8da35bb1-246b-4f12-8eb5-66b438941ae9"
    },
    {
      question: "What eight-legged creature creates intricate webs to catch its prey?",
      choices: ["Bee", "Ant", "Moth", "Spider"],
      correctAnswer: "Spider",
      fact: "Spider webs vary in size and design among different species, but serve the same purpose of ensnaring insects for the spider to feed on.",
      id: "3a87225f-4c18-47b0-a094-56f4c96018cf"
    }
  ]
}

export const PlanetQuestions = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Which of these planets is the largest in our solar system?",
      choices: ["Earth", "Saturn", "Neptune", "Jupiter"],
      correctAnswer: "Jupiter",
      fact: "Jupiter is so large that it could fit over 1,300 Earths inside it. Its immense size makes it the largest planet in our solar system by far.",
      id: "2beabdf7-4642-4e8c-838c-31c32a3475a0"
    },
    {
      question: "Which planet in our solar system is often referred to as the \"Red Planet\"?",
      choices: ["Neptune", "Venus", "Mars", "Earth"],
      correctAnswer: "Mars",
      fact: "The iron oxide (rust) covering the surface gives Mars its reddish color.",
      id: "352f481d-af43-4665-929f-aefb3a59b5cf"
    },
    {
      question: "Which planet in our solar system is known for its beautiful ring system?",
      choices: ["Saturn", "Uranus", "Jupiter", "Pluto"],
      correctAnswer: "Saturn",
      fact: "Saturn's iconic rings, made mostly of ice and rock particles, are its most distinctive feature.",
      id: "d1ebcca3-848b-4791-93d6-09e655d055b7"
    },
    {
      question: "Which planet in our solar system is the only planet to support life?",
      choices: ["Earth", "Mars", "Venus", "Uranus"],
      correctAnswer: "Earth",
      fact: "Earth is the only known planet in the universe where water exists in liquid form on the surface.",
      id: "18499b48-7597-4ec2-a7ac-884256c9c374"
    },
    {
      question: "Which one of these planets was reclassified as a dwarf planet?",
      choices: ["Uranus", "Neptune", "Pluto", "Venus"],
      correctAnswer: "Pluto",
      fact: "Pluto was a former planet that was renamed a dwarf planet in 2006.",
      id: "9d716495-317a-4568-a581-17bd9f34d4a2"
    }
  ]
}

export const RandomQuestions = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Which of these planets is the largest in our solar system?",
      choices: ["Earth", "Saturn", "Neptune", "Jupiter"],
      correctAnswer: "Jupiter",
      fact: "Jupiter is so large that it could fit over 1,300 Earths inside it. Its immense size makes it the largest planet in our solar system by far.",
      id: "2beabdf7-4642-4e8c-838c-31c32a3475a0"
    },
    {
      question: "Which planet in our solar system is often referred to as the \"Red Planet\"?",
      choices: ["Neptune", "Venus", "Mars", "Earth"],
      correctAnswer: "Mars",
      fact: "The iron oxide (rust) covering the surface gives Mars its reddish color.",
      id: "352f481d-af43-4665-929f-aefb3a59b5cf"
    },
    {
      question: "Which planet in our solar system is known for its beautiful ring system?",
      choices: ["Saturn", "Uranus", "Jupiter", "Pluto"],
      correctAnswer: "Saturn",
      fact: "Saturn's iconic rings, made mostly of ice and rock particles, are its most distinctive feature.",
      id: "d1ebcca3-848b-4791-93d6-09e655d055b7"
    },
    {
      question: "Which planet in our solar system is the only planet to support life?",
      choices: ["Earth", "Mars", "Venus", "Uranus"],
      correctAnswer: "Earth",
      fact: "Earth is the only known planet in the universe where water exists in liquid form on the surface.",
      id: "18499b48-7597-4ec2-a7ac-884256c9c374"
    },
    {
      question: "Which one of these planets was reclassified as a dwarf planet?",
      choices: ["Uranus", "Neptune", "Pluto", "Venus"],
      correctAnswer: "Pluto",
      fact: "Pluto was a former planet that was renamed a dwarf planet in 2006.",
      id: "9d716495-317a-4568-a581-17bd9f34d4a2"
    }
  ]
}